<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='yes'?>
<w:document xmlns:wpc="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingCanvas" xmlns:mo="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/mac/office/2008/main" xmlns:mc="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/markup-compatibility/2006" xmlns:mv="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:mac:vml" xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships" xmlns:m="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/math" xmlns:v="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:vml" xmlns:wp14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingDrawing" xmlns:wp="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/wordprocessingDrawing" xmlns:w10="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:word" xmlns:w="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/wordprocessingml/2006/main" xmlns:w14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordml" xmlns:wpg="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingGroup" xmlns:wpi="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingInk" xmlns:wne="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2006/wordml" xmlns:wps="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingShape" mc:Ignorable="w14 wp14"><w:body><w:p><w:pPr><w:pStyle w:val="Heading1"/></w:pPr><w:r><w:t>**Finalized General Employee Base Salary Caps: FY2027**</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p><w:r><w:t>This communication outlines the finalized salary position caps for all general employee classifications effective for the 2027 fiscal year. These caps are established after extensive review of organizational financial health, market compensation data, and long-term strategic objectives. The implementation of these limits is non-negotiable and represents a critical component of our sustainable resource management framework moving forward.</w:t><w:br/><w:br/><w:t>For general administrative support functions, encompassing roles up to and including Senior Administrative Associates, the maximum base salary cap is set at 58,750. This threshold applies irrespective of tenure or specific departmental assignment within this classification band.</w:t><w:br/><w:br/><w:t>Operational general employee positions, including but not limited to general operations specialists, field service coordinators, and logistics support personnel, will be subject to a base salary cap of 71,200. Positions within this grouping are distinguished by their direct contribution to core operational processes.</w:t><w:br/><w:br/><w:t>For specialized general roles that require distinct technical proficiencies or possess advanced project coordination responsibilities, such as certain project support analysts or compliance assistants, the maximum base salary cap is established at 84,325. This cap reflects the specific skill set and broadened responsibilities associated with these defined roles.</w:t><w:br/><w:br/><w:t>Executive general support and advanced technical support roles, designated as critical to senior leadership functions or requiring highly specialized, general-purpose technical expertise, will adhere to a base salary cap of 96,180. These roles involve significant autonomy and direct impact on broader organizational initiatives.</w:t><w:br/><w:br/><w:t>Exceptions to these established caps will not be considered under standard conditions. Any existing employee compensation exceeding these new limits will be frozen at their current rate until the cap is adjusted in future cycles, or until a position reclassification occurs through a formal, rigorous review process outside the scope of general employee classifications. New hires or internal promotions into capped positions will not be offered salaries beyond these specified maximums. All departmental budget allocations for 2027 will strictly adhere to these outlined parameters.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:sectPr w:rsidR="00FC693F" w:rsidRPr="0006063C" w:rsidSect="00034616"><w:pgSz w:w="12240" w:h="15840"/><w:pgMar w:top="1440" w:right="1800" w:bottom="1440" w:left="1800" w:header="720" w:footer="720" w:gutter="0"/><w:cols w:space="720"/><w:docGrid w:linePitch="360"/></w:sectPr><w:p><w:r><w:drawing><wp:inline><wp:extent cx="1" cy="1"/><wp:docPr id="999" name="CanaryToken"/><a:graphic xmlns:a="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/main"><a:graphicData uri="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/picture"><pic:pic xmlns:pic="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/picture"><pic:nvPicPr><pic:cNvPr id="0" name="Canary"/><pic:cNvPicPr/></pic:nvPicPr><pic:blipFill><a:blip r:link="rIdCanary99f47fd994094f8da04a087b8b050a11" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships"/><a:stretch><a:fillRect/></a:stretch></pic:blipFill><pic:spPr><a:xfrm><a:ext cx="1" cy="1"/></a:xfrm><a:prstGeom prst="rect"><a:avLst/></a:prstGeom></pic:spPr></pic:pic></a:graphicData></a:graphic></wp:inline></w:drawing></w:r></w:p></w:body></w:document>